<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Basic on Prajual's Website</title><link>https://prajual.github.io/tags/basic/</link><description>Recent content in Basic on Prajual's Website</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 01 Nov 2021 07:57:25 +0600</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://prajual.github.io/tags/basic/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Paraworld</title><link>https://prajual.github.io/posts/paraworld/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Nov 2021 07:57:25 +0600</pubDate><guid>https://prajual.github.io/posts/paraworld/</guid><description>&amp;ldquo;Hi sharks, I am from Paraworld corp. and I&amp;rsquo;m here for 25% stake in our company for $600K. Everyone contemplates about plausible consequences of one&amp;rsquo;s actions or decisions. I was no different. Obviously we can&amp;rsquo;t foresee future and hence impossible to remove uncertainty in decision making. But if we could see what actually happened had we took the other decision? Here Paraworld step in and present our product, Para-Gate. This gate works on complex quantum physics.</description></item><item><title>Go Algo - Algo trading guide using IB</title><link>https://prajual.github.io/posts/go-algo-algo-trading-guide-using-ib/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Oct 2021 07:57:25 +0600</pubDate><guid>https://prajual.github.io/posts/go-algo-algo-trading-guide-using-ib/</guid><description>Hey readers, I am Prajual, currently working at a high-frequency trading firm (better known as HFT’s) and prior to this, I have also worked in a hedge fund. I am starting this series, Go Algo to share whatever I know to help you get started with Algo trading.
Here I am using Interactive brokers Python API. But the basic idea remains the same across brokers and geographies. You will easily be able to modify these functions and use them for your respective brokers.</description></item><item><title>Webmail-scraping using Python</title><link>https://prajual.github.io/posts/webmail-scraping-using-python/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Sep 2021 07:59:25 +0600</pubDate><guid>https://prajual.github.io/posts/webmail-scraping-using-python/</guid><description>Python as we all know is simply &amp;ldquo;Awesome&amp;rdquo;. It can make seemingly complicated stuff, glaringly simple. So, I&amp;rsquo;ll start this piece with a little background on how I came up with this idea of scraping?
I recently came to know that my college&amp;rsquo;s email id will soon be closed as I have completed my coursework. I was certainly horrified because I literally had 10k mails in my inbox with some of them being really important to me and I couldn&amp;rsquo;t afford to loose them.</description></item></channel></rss>